Sent:	01/01/1980  00:00:00	
 Subject:	Do not delete Organizer note - record in special table '__Files'	


These data matches with original values

Samsung Deal

UK Registration Plates NUMBER S255LMR
*********** 
EDRM Enron Email Data Set has been produced in EML, PST and NSF format by ZL Technologies, Inc. This Data Set is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution 3.0 United States License <http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by/3.0/us/> . To provide attribution, please cite to "ZL Technologies, Inc. (http://www.zlti.com)." 
***********